[
    {
       "question":"In the beginning ____________ created the heavens and the earth",
       "options":[
           "God",
           "Man",
           "Cow",
           "Chicken"
       ],
       "correct" : "God"
    },

    {
        "question":"Adam and Eve had how many children before they died?",
        "options":[
            "Four",
            "Two",
            "Five",
            "Three"
        ],
        "correct":"Three"
    },

    {
        "question":"How old did was Eve when she died?",
        "options":[
            "Not stated in the bible",
            "965",
            "703",
            "565"
        ],
        "correct":"Not stated in the bible"
    },

    {
        "question":"How many wives did Abraham marry before he died?",
        "options":[
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "Four"
        ],
        "correct":"Two"
    },

    {
        "question":"Who was the father of Abraham?",
        "options":[
            "Terah",
            "Nahor",
            "Salah",
            "Arphaxad"
        ],
        "correct":"Terah"
    },

    {
        "question":"How many years did Jacob serve Laban in order to marry Rachael?",
        "options":[
            "Seven",
            "Fourteen",
            "Ten",
            "None of the Above"
        ],
        "correct":"Fourteen"
    },

    {
        "question":"Jacob had how many sons before he died?",
        "options":[
            "13",
            "12",
            "11",
            "7"
        ],
        "correct":"13"
    },

    {
        "question":"___________ changed Jacob's name to Israel?",
        "options":[
            "God",
            "Abraham",
            "Isaac",
            "An Angel"
        ],
        "correct":"God"
    },

    {
        "question":"Esau sold his birth right for_____________?",
        "options":[
            "An amount of money",
            "For His father's blessing",
            "For Jacob's Porridge",
            "To Please God"
        ],
        "correct":"For Jacob's Porridge"
    },
    {
        "question":"Moses got married to _________________",
        "options":[
            "Mariam",
            "Ziporrah",
            "Abigail",
            "Pharoah's daugther"
        ],
        "correct":"Ziporrah"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is not among the ten commandments?",
        "options":[
            "Thou shall not steal",
            "Thou shall love thy neighbour as thy self",
            "Thou shall not commit Adultery",
            "Thou shall not covet thy neighbour's house"
        ],
        "correct": "Thou shall love thy neighbour as thy self"
    },

    {
        "question":"Who was richest man in the bible",
        "options":[
            "King Xerxes of persia",
            "King Solomon",
            "King David",
            "Kind Nebuchadnezzar"
        ],
        "correct": "King Solomon"
    }
]